Hi again, everyone. Uh today we're going
over the um
braces that I sell. Um this is just
going to be the
Micro Draco brace. I have two offerings
um right now, which is medium and or
small and then large. Um
I don't know if you guys remember the
original versions. Um
I've refined [clears throat] them a
couple of times over the months. Um
First one was literally just
I think it was like three parts. I had
to screw them together and then I used
adhesive um and then I used resin over
them. Um
I uh those ones were really durable, but
like they just did not look very good um
in my opinion. Um
Second version um
was a little bit nicer. Um it had like
those little triangle decals on the
sides. Um a little bit stronger.
Third version um was when I had the
plates and then I mounted them onto
that, which is what we're on now. Um and
I have two sizes for those. Um
Small here. They use the exact same
mounting profile as all my other Draco
stuff. Um
I can mount it just as an example for
you guys, but this is it. Um
And then the large the print
orientation, which is manufacturing, is
uh this way. So, it's able to take
direct impacts versus just being flat.
Um
PLA relatively affordable. Um
I want to say it's like 45 for the large
and 30 for the small. Um
However, I'm also releasing
um a new brace, uh which is a PPAGF
folding brace. Um I was initially going
to use TPU for these, but uh
I didn't like the way it flexed um
specifically if you're going to be
shooting shouldering it, which you're
not supposed to, but all of you do.
Um
But yeah, this one is a
the mechanism here. You're going to see
it. And just folds out like this. I
mean, it's, you know, nice and sturdy
for the most part. Um
This is not Well, th- it's going to look
just like this, but yours is going to be
a little more sturdy um cuz I did some
refining since time that I'm going to
making this video. It's going to be a
little bit more uh
What's this called? Um it's like
the folding mechanism is going to be
more like fluent, but it's also going to
stay like a more rigid. Um
But yeah, I can just obviously mount
this relatively straightforward here. We
have our uh
just unscrew the
bottom here.
Make sure you grab the tab
side.
Going along here.
All right. So, for the
um PLA braces, they're just going to be
sit on just like this.
And then
uh use the
the screw mounts.
All right. Just like this. And um I'm
not going to reassemble it cuz it's
unnecessary because I see here the brace
um
the arm fits right in.
And then you can just pull it out one
hand like that.
Um
Small one is uh
same idea. Literally the same front
portion. It's just a very
[clears throat] low profile.
Um
I
don't know how people like to shoot
their guns.
Um so I also don't know how big your
arms are. So like if you're a bigger
guy, get the bigger one. If you're
smaller, get the smaller. But like it's
I don't know. You have options. Just use
your options.
The uh
folding brace, I'll show you guys that
once I get this off and then going to
place it. But uh that one has
the fork design which I had on the
original ones. Um
My reasoning for that is the material is
significantly stronger.
Um
The configuration I have it in is
actually overkill for uh
the
where the weight and pressure
distributions are, but it's okay. Um
so just take your little fork.
Um
This one's fit is going to be tight. Um
and it obviously has to be tight because
it's a folding brace. So you don't want
that like swinging around when you're
going into engage.
Uh let's see here.
Okay.
And here's the folding brace.
Um
Let's see the
how it works.
Folds to the left um of the brace or the
Draco. Um it just folds like so.
Um
and then whenever you want to use it,
just goes like back. Um same concept as
the
other two braces. Um
Get your arm out here
and then engage. Um
This one's obviously a little tighter
here, but yeah.
Same principle.
This one is going to be
has no limitations for heat or anything
like that.
I figured the kind of guys who are going
to be running this folded are going to
keep it in their car or something else.
So, the material's going to have to be a
little bit more heat resistant.
For something like these, the fixed
braces, I would assume they're going to
be used for range use or maybe you just
like fixed braces. Personally, I like
fixed braces.
Um,
I like the way they feel better versus
the folders, but everyone has
preferences, so I like to accommodate
everyone. Um,
Yeah, pretty straightforward. Um,
if you guys have any questions, let me
know. The
PPA brace is probably going to be closer
to 70, 75, which is what my braces were
priced at initially. Um,
you'll notice with all my PLA builds,
um,
prices have come down significantly
because the cost of R&D has been
subsidized by all my early adopters. So,
PPA is a more expensive material, so I
have to charge more regardless, but I've
also put a lot of money in, you know,
such into R&D stuff to make sure this is
a good product, so it's going to
obviously going to start at a higher
price
and then it comes down over time.
Any questions, let me know. Otherwise,
thank you.